We know that there is a lot you want to do as a family, but the more you are the more it costs.
Yes, and we know that it is difficult to make time enough when you have children of different ages.
So in the club we will collect nice deals and discounts-
-To everything from the necessary stuff like grocery bags, to fun experiences that you want to do as a family.
Yes.
We have over the years built up a fairly large experience-
-Kring what our family and our children think is fun to do, and what you think is fun to do.
So we have contacted places that we have been and visited, and they are now in the club with good offers.
- We have built a website with very small means.
- Pytte, Pytte, Pytte.
So, we don't have a lot of money.
And we collaborate with Miia and Ramin, our friends down here who have been seen earlier on the channel.
- Yes, but wait.
Stop, stop.
- Press it down.
"I NEED TO DO IT PERFECT."
Check out, it goes down, because it becomes "wobbly."
Okay.
And you, this is common ...
- I want ice cream!
- You want ice cream.
But we're going to have dinner first, Hörrudu.
- I want ice cream!
- You get ice cream after dinner.
- No, "Göt!"
No, "Göt!"
"Ingot!"
- Porridge.
- Yes.
- But listen, you have to take out the pacifier so I hear.
- Want "Göt!"
Okay.
I can actually imagine boiling some porridge for you.
She is so difficult to get in food right now, so I would like to make oatmeal porridge for her.
But what I would say was that this is ordinary spaghetti, Alma.
Hörrudu, who has eaten wheat -free all year.
Yes!
I have received from my doctor that I am not gluten anymore.
It has grown away.